You've been in Paris for a few days now.
How do you like your new home city? I
can give you an American answer and a
French answer. The American answer would
be this is the greatest city in the
world. This is the best place ever. And
the French answer would be pas mal. Pas
mal.
I know New Orleans is one of the finest
city in the US when it comes to food,
but did you have some time to enjoy
French cuisine? I didn't know how to use
the utensils at first and they had to
show me. So, I felt very American and
I'm sorry, but it was a it was
fantastic. Um
I think it we're excited to have some
food here tonight, but it's
you can't be here long enough. We got to
we're so excited to come back. Did you
ever imagine that you would be running
out to play American football in a
stadium in Paris in your career, Taysom?
Um no. I mean
uh it's kind of crazy cuz you see uh
many international players like uh
Dembélé.
Um
Many guys on PSG. I mean, all over. It's
kind of crazy seeing those guys playing
on that field and just being able to be
on that field it's a it's a blessing for
us. It was amazing. It was amazing. I
think it was the The thing I like the
most about it was I think there's not a
bad seat in the in the stadium. It's
very very circular. Reminds us of the
dome. Um just has the open open top
which we love. So,
um what an honor. I think the coolest
part we were talking about is just
coming from America and it's it seems so
far away to come here and now being
around the people, being around the
culture. Um it feels like a new home and
then we want to go out here and
represent. Uh guys, how important is it
to Mrs. Benson and to the Saints uh to
make history here in the fall? Do Do you
feel like you will be part of history?
I think it's very important. I think
that's why she's made it her mission and
and the New Orleans Saints, the entire
organization. We feel that that bond and
connection and um we want to represent
you all. We want to represent the people
of France. Um that's the best part about
Louisiana in my opinion is the people
and the culture and and how strongly we
protect our own and and we're obviously
not from there, but we've they've kind
of adopted us and and Miss Benson um in
particular. So, we want to represent you
all and and go out there and and win.
Guys, it will be some people's first
interaction with American football in
France. That That will be the first time
they see American football with you
guys. What does it feel like to be an
ambassador, Taysom?
It's crazy cuz uh you know, I didn't
think I'd get this far in football, but
just being here just to uh kind of
express the American football here is uh
it's good feeling cuz uh you see a lot
of kids out here playing flag football
and everything, but
you know, hopefully we can uh you know,
get American football more bigger out
here. So, it'll be fun.
Yeah, you see the you see the passion
about football here in France and you
see the passion about American football
as well. And I think we have that
passion that we've grown up as kids and
and learned it in America and
uh we want to bring that here. We want
to bring that everywhere as far as just
the
um watching American football game is a
it's a feeling like no other and it's
comparable to football here. So, it's um
we're we're just excited and thankful to
even be here cuz we we feel very
undeserving and we feel um very honored
um more than anything. Taysom, Taylor,
you're obviously the quarterback your
first season
How excited are you for next season?
Uh I'm fired up. I can't wait. We've
been Ty and I have been training every
single day. We've been working out. Um
we're just itching to play again. I
think you see the vision of the front
office. You see the vision of coach
Kellen Moore um of Gayle Benson and and
I think everybody's on the same page and
we want to we want to go out there and
win it all and do everything that we
can. I think that we know we can do a
lot of things in this league right now.
First thing we just got to win the
division, but you know, uh
I think we're we're coming up right now.
So. Do you have a message uh for budding
French players who want to make it in
the NFL?
You know, just keep going. Follow your
dreams. There's nothing that can hold
you back as long as you believe you can
do it. Cuz your period mostly in the
shadow, your job is basically to protect
Taysom from the opponent. What makes a
good offensive lineman like you? Um I
think a big thing is just communication.
You know, uh there's five of us that are
trying to protect this guy and we have
to be in uh the same same uh
you know, uh wavelength and everything
with it, you know, so if we're not on
the same page, we can't protect this
guy, but you know, he's the the big arm
and everything. We got to get him going.
So. Communication, a bit of working out,
too? Yeah, a bit of working out, yeah.
Got to stay off the food, huh?
So, Taylor, how much do you like these
guys, the offensive lineman? I suppose
you are always nice to them. Got We got
to. We go to eat We go to dinner every
Thursday. Um
and that's the best part about New
Orleans and now and now France is we
find a new restaurant to go eat and just
break bread and have fun and um they're
the best guys on the team because he's
being humble, but he's 300 and
30 lb. How old is he? I mean, 315? I
don't know.
He's 300 plus lb, but he can run
20 mph and he he can jump and he's the
the most athletic people on the field
and that's why they're the most
important. So, um obviously my role is
is is spread out um and and there's a
lot of direction and obviously passing
the ball to the other guys um
on the field and
um it's a great great honor though. It's
And that's the best part why we love
American football. We feel like it's the
one of the best team sports is because
it takes everybody. Taylor, everybody in
the world knows what a quarterback is
thanks to TV, films, Netflix, the the
series quarterbacks, but can you
describe how difficult this position is
and how much information you need to
process in real time?
Um yeah, it's it's
it's incredibly difficult, but that's
why you love it. And I think the biggest
thing is you have the ball in your hands
every single play and more than anything
you have to know what everybody else is
doing on the field on on your offense
and you also all have to know what the
entire defense is doing and their job is
to throw you off and try and disguise
and
um there's 100 plus different plays in
you know, different formations or set
pieces in soccer and there's 100 plus
different formations and then that we
can get into at any certain point of
time. So, um the biggest part is the
mental like he was talking about. You
see the physicality of of football, but
more than anything it's the the mental
side. Any personal goals for this
season, guys? I think we we got to win
the division. I think it starts with We
have it We have team success um and that
leads to individual success. Um
we want to win the division. We want to
win the Super Bowl. And and then after
that, that's where all the fun things
happen. And so, that's that's our main
goal. Um like you said, winning the
division. Uh starts with one game at a
time, but we're trying to win in the
locker room first, you know, if we can't
beat each other up at practice first,
then we can't win the games out there.
So. Uh on a last note, guys, you guys
are being ambassadors of your sport and
your team. Why should all French people
now be Saints fan? I'll let you I'll
give you the floor to give your
arguments.
Well, other than the the obvious
connection of the the French Louisiana
connection, but we got the most We have
the most fun. We have the most swag. We
got a young team. We got a bunch of a
young young and up-and-coming guys. We
want to have fun. We want to bring
energy to the field. The black and gold,
you can't miss it. You got the We got
the best swag, the best gear. Um
and we and we want to go out there and
win. We got to go out there and we want
to represent you all more than anything.
I think that's the best part about
Louisiana like I said is the passion.
So, we want to bring that here. Uh the
community out there, man. You know, you
got stuff like Mardi Gras and stuff like
you know, you want to party all that?
Just come over, man. It's it's a it's a
fun experience and everything. So,
just come out there and we'll we'll
we'll take care of you guys.
Yeah. And we'll finish on that. Thank
you so much, guys.